- Boston Public Library Witchcraft Documents
  - Walcott, Mary v. Susannah Martin Reverse side, MsAm45
  - Willard, John Examination,version 1 18 May 1692 multiple pages, MsAm46
  - Willard, John Examination, version 2 18 May 1692 mutiple pages, MsAm46
  - Putnam, Ann v. John Willard Reverse side, MsAm47
  - Nurse, Rebecca et al Death Warrant Reverse side, MsAm48
  - Walcott, Mary v. John Willard Reverse side, MsAm49
  - Wilkins, Daniel Inquest Reverse side, MsAm50
  - Complaint v. John Willard Bottom portion Reverse side, MsAm51
  - Walcott, Mary v. Ann Foster 15 July 1692 Reverse side, MsAm52
  - Walcott, Mary Hubbard, Eliz v. Ann Foster, MsAm1147.1
  - Walcott, Mary v. Rebecca Eames, MsAm1147.2
  - Williams, Abigail v. John Willard, MsAm1147.3
  - Complaint v. Margaret Hawkes, MsCh1.154
  - Cole, Sarah Warrant, MsCh1.88
  - Carrell & Coal Warrant & Return, MsCh2.12/13
  - Dod, Thomas Kesor, Elizer Recognizance, MsCh.2.44
  - Edwards, Mary v. Rachel Clenton, MsCh.2.60
  - Fuller, James, Jr v. Rachel Clenton, MsCh.2.68
  - Dolliver, Ann Examination Multiple images, MsCh.2.194
  - Ireson, Mary Examination Multiple images, MsCh.2.194
  - Stephens, Sarah Pasque, Margaret v. Rebecca Nurse et al, MsCh.2.110
  - Jackson, John Examination, MsCh.2.448
  - Emerson, Martha Warrant, MsCh.2.28
  - Dier, Eliz. Prince, Margaret Warrant, MsCh.2.50
  - Hutchins, Wilford Warrant, MsCh.2.92
  - Barker, Mary & Wm Marstone Warrant, MsAmCh.2.108
  - Complaint v. Mary Clark, MsCh.2.156
  - Marshall, Mary v. Colson, MsCh.2.187
  - Hill, Zebulon v. Peney, MsCh.2.198
  - Post, Mary Warrant, MsCh.2.204
  - Carrier, Richard & Andrew Warrant, MsCh.2.208
  - Jackson, Sr., Jr. Warrant, MsCh.2.222
  - Bishop, Bridget Warrant (photo copy), MsCh.2.266
  - Johnson, Abigail & Eliz Complaint, MsCh..2.350
  - Lacey, Mary, Jr. Warrant - Ballard, MsCh.2.400
  - Parris, Ingersoll Putnam v. Eliz. Procter, MsCh.2.500
  - Jacobs, Geo Andrew, Daniel Warrant 17May 1692, MsCh.A.K.48
  - Alden, John, et al Bond, 31 Dec 1692, F. 10.47
  - Browne, John v. Goodwife Cole 3 Oct 1692, MsF.1.7
  - Foster & Tyler v. John Jackson, Jr., MsCh2.196
  - Swan, Robert v. Mary Clark, MsCh2.245
  - Peney, Joan Warrant, MsCh2.249
  - Bridges, Mary Warrant, MsCh2.349
  - Ballard, Joseph v. Mary Lacey 19 July 1692, MsCh2.401
  - Complaint of Several 28 May 1692 Reverse, MsAm44